If you open up the Boston Housing XGBoost hyperparameter tuning high-level notebook,
请打开 Boston Housing - XGBoost (Hyperparameter Tuning) - High Level notebook
which I've already done here,
我已经打开了
and then execute the first few cells and scroll down
并执行了前几个单元格
to the part where we want to train the XGBoost model.
向下滚动到训练 XGBoost 模型部分
To begin with, we construct an estimator object in
首先 我按照训练单个模型时的步骤
exactly the same way as if we were just training a single model.
构建了一个 estimator 对象
Essentially, this is going to be used as the base model which SageMaker will
SageMaker 将以该对象为基准模型
change and tweak in order to test various hyperparameters.
进行更改调整 以测试各种超参数
Next, we will actually set some hyperparameters.
接着设置一些超参数
Now again, this is going to be the base model from which SageMaker will depart.
这是基准模型 SageMaker 将以其为基础加以更改
So, by default, we'll set eta to 0.2,
例如 默认地我们将 eta 设为 0.2
for example, although we may allow SageMaker to vary that later on.
但是稍后允许 SageMaker 更改它
So now, we've set up our estimator object,
设置好 estimator 对象后
it's time to create a new object which in this case
我们将创建一个新的对象
is called a hyperparameter tuner object.
称为 HyperparameterTuner 对象
To begin with, we give it an estimator object which acts as the base model.
首先 将基准模型设为 estimator 对象
We tell it how to differentiate between two different trained models.
指定如何区分两个不同的已训练模型
In our case, we are going to use the RMSE metric, and in particular,
我们将使用 RMSE 指标
we care about the metric applied to the validation data set,
我们关心的是应用到验证集的指标
not the training data set.
而不是训练集的指标
Next, we want to find the model that minimizes the validation RMSE.
接着 寻找最小化验证 RMSE 的模型
Max jobs says how many models we want sage maker to train in total.
max_jobs 表示我们总共希望 SageMaker 训练多少个模型
Max parallel jobs says how many models we
max_parallel_jobs 表示我们希望
want sage maker to train in parallel with one another.
SageMaker 并行训练多少个模型
Lastly, we tell SageMaker what different ranges we want to give specific hyperparameters.
最后 指定特定超参数的范围
So, for example, this eta hyper-parameter,
例如 指定超参数 eta
we tell SageMaker that it should be a continuous parameter in the range 0.05 to 0.5.
应该是连续超参数 范围是 0.05 到 0.5
Once we've created the hyperparameter tuner object,
创建了 HyperparameterTuner 对象后
we simply call fit on
与 estimator 对象一样
that hyperparameter tuning object in the same way as we would on an estimator object.
对该对象调用 fit() 方法
Now, much like some of the other training jobs that we've constructed in the past,
就像我们之前创建的大部分其他训练作业一样
the work that SageMaker is doing is happening in the background.
SageMaker 将在后台执行操作
If we want to have a visual representation of what's going on,
如果要直观地查看进度
we need to use the weight method.
需要使用 wait() 方法
Now, we wait for the hyperparameter tuning job to complete.
下面等待超参数优化作业运行完毕
Now that SageMaker has finished training a bunch of models for us,
现在 SageMaker 已经训练完一批模型
we can take a look and see what the best trained model was.
我们看看训练的最佳模型是哪个
This is stored in the best training job method.
它存储在 best_training_job 方法中
As we can see, this is the name of the best training job.
这是最佳训练作业的名称
In the past when we wanted to create
之前 当我们想要创建 transformer 对象
a transformer object in order to create a batch transform job to test our model,
以便创建批转换作业来测试模型时
we did so using an estimator object.
我们使用了 estimator 对象
However, we don't have an estimator object which has been trained.
但是我们没有已经训练过的 estimator 对象
We created an estimator object earlier in order
我们之前创建了一个 estimator 对象
to create the hyperparameter tuner object.
以便创建 HyperparameterTuner 对象
However, the original estimator object has not been trained.
但是原始 estimator 对象没有训练
What we can do is create a new estimator object using the attach method,
我们可以创建一个新的 estimator 对象
and attach this estimator object to a training job.
然后使用 attach 方法将此 estimator 对象附加到训练作业上
This will result in creating an estimator object that is trained.
这样将会创建一个训练过的 estimator 对象
In fact, is associated with the model artifacts that are
实际上 它与作为参数传入的训练作业
created as a result of the training job that we pass in as a parameter.
创建的模型工件相关联
In this case, we're passing in the name of the best training job.
我们在这里传入最佳训练作业的名称
So, xgb-attached is now the trained estimator object
xgb-attached 现在是与超参数优化作业生成的
associated with the best training job from our hyperparameter tuning job.
最佳训练作业相关联的已训练 estimator 对象
From there, we can do the same stuff that we did before when testing our model.
然后我们可以执行与测试模型时一样的步骤
That is, we create a transformer and then start our transform job.
创建一个 transformer 然后开始转换作业
Waiting to see what the results are.
等待结果
Now that the batch transform has finished up,
批量转换运行完毕后
we can copy the resulting output back to our local notebook instance,
将生成的输出复制到本地 notebook 实例中
and then create a nice little chart to see how well we did.
然后绘制图形 看看效果如何